<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Home Workout</string>
        <string name="jumingjack">Start with your feet together and your arms by your sides, then jump up with your feet apart and your hands overhead.
        Return to the start position then do the next rep.
        his exercise provides a full-body workout and works all your large muscle groups.</string>
    <string name="inclinepushup">Start in the regular push-up position but with your hands elevated on a chair or bench.
        Then push your body up down using yourarm strength.
        Remember to keep your body straight.</string>
    <string name="kneepushup">let your knees touch the floor and raise your feet up off the floor.
        Next push your body up and down.</string>
    <string name="pushup">Lay prone on the ground with arms supporting your body.
        Keep your body straight while raising and lowering your body with your armsThis exercise works the chest, shoulders, triceps, back and legs.</string>
    <string name="widearmpushup">Start in the regular push-up position but with your hands spread wider than your shoulders.
        Then push your body up and down.
        Remember to keep your body straight.</string>
    <string name="cobrastrecth">Lie down on your stomach and bend your elbows with your hands beneath your shouldersThen push your chest up off the ground as far as possible.
        Hold this position for seconds.</string>
    <string name="cheststretch">Find a doorway, take a lunge position in the doorway with your arms on the doorframe and your elbows a little lower than your shoulders, then slowly bring your chest forward.
        Hold this position for 30-40 seconds.
        Then slowly come out of it, bring your arms down and do a couple of shoulder rolls.</string>
    <string name="armraises">Stand on the floor with your arms extended straight forward at shoulder height.
        Raise your arms above your head.Return</string>
    <string name="sidearmraises">Stand with your feet shoulder width apartRaise your arms to the sides at shoulder height, then put them down.
        Repeat the exercise.Keep your arms straight during the exercise.</string>
    <string name="tricepsdips">For the start position, sit on the chair.
        Then move your hip off the chair with your hands holding the edge of the chair.
        Slowly bend and stretch your arms to make your body go up and down.
        This is a great exercise for the triceps.</string>
    <string name="armcirclesclickwise">Stand on the floor with your arms extended straight out to the sides at shoulder height.
        Move your arms clockwise in circles fast.
        Try to do it as fast as you can.
        It a great exercise for the deltoid muscle.</string>
    <string name="armcirclescounterclickwise">Stand on the floor with your arms extended straight out to the sides at shoulder height.
        Move your arms counterclockwise in circlesfast.
        Try to do it as fast as you can.
        It a great exercise for the deltoid muscle. </string>
    <string name="diamondpushups">Start in the push-up position.
        Make a diamond shape with your forefingers and thumbs together under your chest.
        Then push your body up and down.
        Remember to keep your body straight.</string>
    <string name="chestpresspulse">Hold your forearms together at shoulder height and bend your elbows with your hands together to make an L shape.
        Then lift your forearms up and down.</string>
    <string name="legbrbellcurlleft">Stand against a wall.
        Lift your right leg up, lean forward and grab underneath your right ankle with your left hand.
        Bring the ankle up towards the shoulder as much as you can, then lower it and repeat the exercise.</string>
    <string name="legbrbellcurlright">Stand against a wall.
        Lift your left leg up, lean forward and grab underneath your left ankle with your right hand.
        Bring the ankle up towards the shoulder as much as you can, then lower it and repeat the exercise.</string>
    <string name="diagonalplank">Start in the straight arm plank position.
        Lift your right arm and left leg until they are parallel with the ground.
        Return to the start position and repeat with the other side.</string>
    <string name="punches">Stand with one of your legs forward and your knees bent slightly.
        Bend your elbows and clench your fists in front of your face.
        Extend one arm forward with the palm facing the floor.
        Take the arm back and repeat with the other arm.</string>
    <string name="pushupspushups">Lay prone on the ground with arms supporting your body.
        Keep your body straight while raising and lowering your body with your arms.
        This exercise works the chest, shoulders, triceps, back and legs.</string>
    <string name="inchworms">Start with your feet shoulder width apart.
        Bend your body and walk your hands in front of you as far as you can, then walk your hands back.
        Repeat the exercise.</string>
    <string name="wallpushups">Stand in front of a wall one big step away from it.
        Then put your hands out straight towards the wall and lean against it.
        Lift your heels.
        Slowly bend your elbows and press your upper body towards the wall.
        Push back and repeat the exercise.
        Remember to keep your body straight.</string>
    <string name="tricepsstretchleft">Put your left hand on your back, use your right hand to grab your left elbow and gently pull it.
        Hold this position for a few seconds.</string>
    <string name="tricepsstretchright">Put your right hand on your back, use your left hand to grab your right elbow and gently pull it.
        Hold this position for a few seconds.</string>
    <string name="standingbicepsstretchleft">LEFT Stand with your left arm close to a wall.
        Extend your left arm and put your left handon the wall, then gently turn your body to theright.</string>
    <string name="standingbicepsstretchright">RIGHT Stand with your right arm close to a wall.
        Extend your right arm and put your righthand on the wall, then gently turn your bodyto the left.</string>
    <string name="abodominalcrunches">Lie on your back with your knees bent andyour arms stretched forward.
        Then lift your upper body off the floor.
        Hold for a few seconds and slowly return.
        It primarily works the rectus abdominis muscle and the obliques.</string>
    <string name="russiantwist">Sit on the floor with your knees bent, feet lifted a little bit and back tilted backwards.
        Then hold your hands together and twistfrom side to side.</string>
    <string name="mountainclimber">Start in the push-up position.
        Bend your right knee towards your chest and keep your left leg straight, then quickly switch from one leg to the other.This exercise strengthens multiple muscle groups.</string>
    <string name="heeltouch">Lie on the ground with your legs bent andyour arms by your sides.
        Slightly lift your upper body off the floor and make your hands alternately reach yourheels.</string>
    <string name="legraises">Lie down on your back, and put your hands beneath your hips for support.
        Then lift your legs up until they form a rightangle with the floor.
        Slowly bring your legs back down and repeat the exercise.</string>
    <string name="plank">Lie on the floor with your toes and forearms on the ground.
        Keep your body straight and hold this position as long as you can.
        This exercise strengthens the abdomen,back and shoulders.</string>
    <string name="spinelumbertwiststretchleft">Lie on your back with your legs extended.
        Lift your left leg up and use your right hand to pull your left knee to the right, but keep your other arm extended to the side on the floor.
        Hold this position for a few seconds.</string>
    <string name="spinelumbertwiststretchright">Lie on your back with your legs extended.
        Lift your right leg up and use your left hand to pull your right knee to the left, but keep your other arm extended to the side on the floor.
        Hold this position for a few seconds.</string>
    <string name="sidehop">Stand on the floor, put your hands in front of you and hop from side to side.</string>
    <string name="squats">Stand with your feet shoulder width apart and your arms stretched forward, then lower your body until your thighs are parallel with the floor.
        Your knees should be extended in the same direction as your toes.
        Return to the start position and do the next rep.
        This works the thighs, hips buttocks, quads, hamstrings and lower body.</string>
    <string name="sidelayinglegliftleft">Lie down on your side with your head rested on your right arm.
        Lift your upper leg up and return to the start position.
        Make sure your left leg goes straight up anddown during the exercise.
        Its a great exercise for the gluteus.</string>
    <string name="sidelayinglegliftright">Lie down on your side with your head rested on your left arm.
        Lift your upper leg up and return to the start position.
        Make sure your right leg goes straight up and down during the exercise.
        Its a great exercise for the gluteus.</string>
    <string name="backwarglunge">Stand with your feet shoulder width apart and your hands on your hips.
        Step a big step backward with your right leg and lower your body until your left thigh is parallel to the floor.
        Return and repeat with the other side.</string>
    <string name="donkeykicksleft">Start on all fours with your knees under your butt and your hands under your shoulders.
        Then lift your left leg and squeeze your butt as much as you can.
        Go back to the startposition and repeat the exercise.</string>
    <string name="donkeykicksright">Start on all fours with your knees under butt and your hands under shoulders.
        Then lift your right leg and squeeze your butt as much as you can.
        Go back to the startposition and repeat the exercise.</string>
    <string name="start_in_the_regular_push_up_position_but_with_your_hands_elevated_on_a_chair_or_bench_then_push_your_body_up_down_using_yourarm_strength_remember_to_keep_your_body_straight">Start in the regular push-up position but with your hands elevated on a chair or bench. Then push your body up down using yourarm strength. Remember to keep your body straight.</string>



</resources>